[
    {
      "number": "1",
      "question": "Who is known as 'Swor Samrat'?",
      "option1": "Nabin K bhattarai",
      "option2": "Anju Panta",
      "option3": "Narayan Gopal",
      "option4": "Sugam Pokharel",
      "correctAnswer": "option3"
    },
    {
      "number": "2",
      "question": "Who is the singer of 'Lakhau Hajarau'?",
      "option1": "Yabesh Thapa",
      "option2": "Samir Shrestha",
      "option3": "Shashwot Khadka",
      "option4": "bekcha",
      "correctAnswer": "option1"
    },
    {
      "number": "3",
      "question": "Which Nepali band sang 'Bagaicha'?",
      "option1": "1974 AD",
      "option2": "Nepathya",
      "option3": "Kta haru",
      "option4": "Phosphenes",
      "correctAnswer": "option3"
    },
    {
      "number": "4",
      "question": "Which song is this from: 'Kalo lamo pareli kesha'?",
      "option1": "Malai nasodha",
      "option2": "Gajalu ti thula thula aakha",
      "option3": "Tutnu Thiyo Tutyo Mutu",
      "option4": "Kehi Mitho Baat Gara",
      "correctAnswer": "option2"
    },
    {
      "number": "5",
      "question": "Who is the first rapper of Nepal?",
      "option1": "Uniq Poet",
      "option2": "Yama Buddha",
      "option3": "Girish Khatiwada",
      "option4": "Laure",
      "correctAnswer": "option3"
    },
    {
      "number": "6",
      "question": "Who is the singer for 'Aaudai Jadai'?",
      "option1": "The Uglyz",
      "option2": "Kush",
      "option3": "1974 AD",
      "option4": "Ulto Pulto",
      "correctAnswer": "option1"
    },
    {
      "number": "7",
      "question": "What is the most viewed Nepali song in YouTube?",
      "option1": "Saali Man Paryo",
      "option2": "Phul Butte Sari",
      "option3": "Gojima Daam Chaina",
      "option4": "Kutu ma kutu",
      "correctAnswer": "option4"
    },
    {
      "number": "8",
      "question": "Which song is the lyrics 'K yei nai ho astitto mero' from?",
      "option1": "Bhanai - Tribal Rain",
      "option2": "Putali - The Elements",
      "option3": "Bachau - Albratoss",
      "option4": "Narisawna - Tribal Rain",
      "correctAnswer": "option1"
    },
    {
      "number": "9",
      "question": "Who is the most viewed song of Bipul Chhetri on spotify?",
      "option1": "Syndicate",
      "option2": "Aashish",
      "option3": "Ram Sailee",
      "option4": "Asaar",
      "correctAnswer": "option1"
    },
    {
      "number": "10",
      "question": "Who is the singer of 'Mohani lagla hai'?",
      "option1": "Naryan Gopal",
      "option2": "Arun Thapa",
      "option3": "Nepathya",
      "option4": "Albatross",
      "correctAnswer": "option1"
    }
  ]
  